http://www.betterbidding.com/index.php?privacy

Privacy Policy - Priceline Coupons, Hotwire Hotels Revealed, Hotel Lists, Bidding Help
Introduction
Your privacy is of the utmost importance to BetterBidding. Our basic principles are:
We respect your privacy at BetterBidding
You control your personal Information,
We try to limit our collection of personal Information as needed to provide and improve our services to you,
We do not disclose your personal Information to third parties unless we need to do so to fulfill your requests, you expressly tell us to, we believe we are reasonably compelled to do so, or we are required to by law.
BetterBidding's services contain links to other web sites outside BetterBidding. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This privacy policy only governs Information collected on BetterBidding.com.
What Information is Gathered
We collect the Information you give us when you become a member of BetterBidding.
Site Visitors
In general, you can browse most parts of the site without registering, but to use some features (including posting) you will need to register (and validate your account via clicking a link in the email sent) in order to post on the site.
Browser and Other Information We May Collect
In addition to the Information we collect when you register for an account, BetterBidding also collects certain technical and other information about the online activities of our users (whether they have registered or not). This may include, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser type, and operating system.
We have the ability to view your IP address if you visit BetterBidding.
We also collect the Information that you provide when you make a post so that we can archive and display your posts.
Member Emails
As a registered member, you must agree to receive our system emails. URL tracking may be used in some of these emails in order to track response rates and other aspects which may help us improve the services provided. URL tracking may use cookies.
International Visitors
Like almost every Web site, BetterBidding may be accessed by an international audience. By visiting our Web site and providing us with Information, you acknowledge and agree that your Information may be processed for the purposes identified in this policy. In addition, such Information may be stored on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction, which may have more or less stringent privacy practices than your own. By providing us with your Information, you consent to the transfer of such Information.
How Information is Used
We understand that you value your personally identifiable Information. We generally use your personal Information to render you services and to improve our services.
We may use your personal and registration Information to: improve our services; troubleshoot problems; measure consumer interest in our products and services; inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our Terms of Use; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection and in this policy. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems, and in particular we may examine your personal Information to identify users using multiple User IDs or aliases.
Email Communications from BetterBidding
BetterBidding may send you messages through our messaging system to keep you apprised of your membership status, site developments, and to inform you of new offers.
Third Party Use and Partner Site Email Communications
BetterBidding may have or initiate partnerships with other Web-based services. Some of these arrangements may include the sharing of some of your personal Information with our partners in order to extend these services to you. We only share Information when you specifically authorize it.
BetterBidding, as well as its partner sites, may send you e-mail messages on a regular basis to keep you apprised of your membership status, site developments, and to inform you of new offers. Examples of this include special offers from our business partners. Included in each of these messages are simple instructions on how to remove yourself from these mailings if you do not wish to receive them in the future.
Third Party Sharing to Render Services to You
We may use third parties to help us perform services, such as transmitting emails and other service-related functions. If these third parties require access to your Information in order to provide their services, they will be obligated to abide by this privacy policy when handling your Information. We require third party service providers to limit their use of your personal Information to rendering services for us and you consistent with this policy.
Disclosure of Personal Information
Your personally identifiable Information, is not sold to others. There are some situations where we may need to disclose Information to organizations or entities not described in our policy here. BetterBidding may be required to disclose your personal Information: (i) if we believe it is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process (such as a court order, subpoena, search warrant, etc.) or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; (ii) would potentially mitigate our liability in an actual or potential lawsuit; (iii) is otherwise necessary to protect our rights or property; or that of others (iv) is necessary to protect the interest of other users of our web site.
Merger or Sale of BetterBidding
We may transfer the Information in our possession in connection with a sale of assets of the company, a sale of the company or a merger.
Respecting Others' Privacy
By agreeing to our Terms of Use, you agree that, with respect to other users' personal Information that you obtain through the site or through a BetterBidding-related communication or BetterBidding-facilitated transaction, BetterBidding hereby grants to you a license to use such Information only for: (a) BetterBidding-related personal communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages, (b) using services offered through BetterBidding, and (c) any other purpose that a user expressly agrees to after you tell them the purpose you would like to use it for. In all cases, you must give users an opportunity to remove themselves from your systems and a chance to review what information you have collected about them. In addition, under no circumstances, except as defined in this paragraph, can you disclose personal information about another user to any third party without our consent and the consent of that user. You agree that other users may use your personal Information to communicate with you in accordance with this paragraph.
BetterBidding and our members do not tolerate spam. Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, you are not licensed to add a BetterBidding member to your mailing list (email, including the BetterBidding site?s messaging systems, or physical mail) without their express consent. To report BetterBidding related spam, please contact us using our legal form.
Security of Information
Your Information is stored on BetterBidding's servers located in the United States. We use procedural and technical safeguards to protect your personal Information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy.
That being said, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet and no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be absolutely secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal Information, BetterBidding cannot ensure or warrant the security of any Information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure the security of your Information on our systems.
Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account Information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member Information at any time. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal Information or private communications will always remain private.
If BetterBidding learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using this web site or providing personal Information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of this site. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us.
Cookies, Web Beacons and Personalization
"Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests.
BetterBidding uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session Information for purposes including: ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements; to customize advertising and Web page content based on browser type and user profile Information; to estimate and report our total audience size and traffic; and to conduct research to improve our content and services. We do not link the Information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable Information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies.
We may use third party advertisers to display advertisements on some of our pages. These advertisers may use their own cookies and these are be subject to the advertiser?s own privacy policies, not the BetterBidding privacy policy.
BetterBidding may use various technical methods to research certain usage and activities on its and our website. The Information collected is used to find out more about our users; for more accurate reporting; and to improve the effectiveness of our marketing. No personally identifiable Information about you is shared by BetterBidding as a result of this research.
You agree that we may use your personal Information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information.
Children
We at BetterBidding believe it essential that parents are involved in their children's online experiences. That is why, in compliance with federal law, we do not knowingly collect personal information of any kind from anyone under the age of 13. If we become aware of a user under the age of 13 providing information on our site, we will terminate their account and purge our databases of all Information provided by that user.
Access to and Changing Information
Once you become a member of BetterBidding, the Information you provide is stored in the site. You may access or change most of this Information at any time through your account?s control panel.
Notice of Modifications
In the future, BetterBidding may update and revise its privacy policy. We will provide notice on our website if we decide to change our privacy policy in a way that would be materially less restrictive than this policy. If you continue to use BetterBidding, you will be accepting the new policies. If you choose to opt out of the new policy, you must notify us in writing and will no longer be able to participate as a member. The effective date of this policy is February 15, 2012.
Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account Information.
Questions?
If you have any questions about this privacy policy still unanswered after reviewing this policy, please do not hesitate to contact us.
Attn: Privacy Officer
BetterBidding.com
PO Box 1895
Hoboken, NJ 07030
Third Parties
Google Analytics
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.
Privacy Policy
Spam Defense
The IPS Spam Defense Service passes the email address and IP address of the registering member to the service to determine the likelihood a registering account is a spam source.
Privacy Policy
Invisible reCAPTCHA
This site uses a CAPTCHA to ensure humans are performing certain actions. The CAPTCHA provider may set a session cookie and get information about your internet browser and device accessing this website.
Privacy Policy
New Content
Priceline and Hotwire
Privacy Policy
QUICKQUOTE
[X]
PRICELINE & HOTWIRE on one screen!
Age of child:
FINDFAST[X]
Room %roomN%:
Adults
Children
Age of child:
FINDFAST[X]
EXCLUSIVELY at BetterBidding:
5% OFF
PRICELINE COUPON
(click here) and use promo code: BBOCT20
(Express Deals or PrePaid Hotels / 3+ stars / 2+ nites... expires 10/31/2020)
OR
7% OFF
HOTWIRE COUPON
(click here) and use promo code: AUTUMN
(Hot Rate Hotels ... expires 10/11/2020)
OR
$10 OFF
PRICELINE COUPON
(click here) and use promo code: PICK10HTL
(Express Hotel Deals / $100+ purchase... expires 10/09/2020)
About Us
Contact Us
BetterBidding.com®Terms of Use / Privacy Policy
Powered by Invision Community
